Well,
after that,
I went to her place again
for dinner.
She said a lot of harsh things
to Mr. Gao right in front of me,
triggering his heart attack.
The next time I saw her
was at the hospital.
Chairman.
I came to see you.
Are you feeling better?
I'm fine.
Heart condition.
It's an old issue.
Yanyan, take his things.
Feng Shu,
your eyes give you away.
You haven't known our Yanyan for long,
but
you really like her,
don't you?
I...
Come sit.
Why is a grown man being so shy?
Yanyan,
stop busying yourself.
Listen to Dad.
Feng Shu
has always been by my side.
He is
capable,
responsible,
and can support this family.
Most importantly,
he can take good care of you.
Dad hopes that
both of you
will be happy together.
Fengshu,
can you do that?
I...
Yanyan, say something.
Chairman, we can do it.
So, Mr. Feng,
according to you,
from the dinner at their house
that caused the argument,
to the hospital
where Gao Yayan accepted you,
was it about three to five days?
Let's just say three days.
Okay, three days.
Did her attitude do a 180
just because her dad was hospitalized,
or was there another reason?
Captain Weng,
does the reason for her change in attitude
really matter?
Didn't I tell you before?
It makes no difference
to the outcome.
She agreed to be with me.
Hello.
She's in a really bad state.
I'm afraid she'll break down.
If worse comes to worst,
I'll turn myself in.
She agreed to be with me.
Later,
the old man even said
he'd organize
a small
engagement ceremony for us.
She didn't refuse.
That's enough.
When is it?
I mean
the time for the engagement ceremony
you mentioned.
I remember this time very clearly.
It was the day
our chairman had the accident.
Thank you.
None for me.
Okay.
Have a seat.
Alright.
Yayan,
Feng,
about the engagement ceremony
I mentioned last time,
have you thought about it?
I have no problem with it, of course.
Don't laugh at me, Mr. Gao,
but I'd
get married right now if I could.
Smooth talker.
Feng,
patience is a virtue.
But I admire your courage.
That's an improvement.
Yayan,
Dad really wants to know
what you think.
I think
we should do it.
And if we do it, let's make it big.
I want to invite more friends over.
After the ceremony,
we can throw a big party.
It'll be great for everyone to drink
and have fun together.
Yanyan,
I'm not joking.
Dad
is seriously asking for your opinion.
I've thought about it.
First,
we invite all the political
and business elites here that day.
We can take this opportunity
to promote communication.
Xiaofeng,
will your parents have time to come?
Of course they will.
And I think
since it's an engagement ceremony,
we shouldn't be afraid of making it grand.
We should invite the media too,
so it'll be impressive enough.
Yes,
I've already consulted them.
They're flying back from abroad.
We just need to schedule it in advance.
So everything is
all set.
Leave the rest
to me.
Thank you, Mr. Gao.
Thanks, Dad.
Nanny,
Get the car ready.
Okay.
You two go ahead and eat.
I'll walk you out.
It's raining outside.
Maybe you shouldn't visit my mom today.
You can go tomorrow morning
when it clears up.
Rain or shine.
A little rain
is nothing.
Yanyan,
you're worrying about your dad now.
You've grown up.
What are you doing?
I didn't do anything.
I just wanted to...
Want to what?
Don't even think about it.
Get back to your own house.
Aunt Wu, see him out.
That's how it was.
So like I said,
she didn't refuse.
That's enough.
Realistic enough.
Captain Li,
'realistic'
is a total compliment in my book.
I appreciate it, Captain Li.
Thank you.
Bullshit.
He's full of lies.
Now he's
throwing mud at us, right?
Calm down.
Listen to what Xingchen has to say.
Exactly.
We came here instead of the station,
Exactly. We came here
instead of the station,
If I really suspected your boyfriend,
I'd have summoned him
and cuffed him.
Cuffed him?
Why else would we be at your house?
Right, right, right.
The thing is,
I know Feng Shu pretty well.
He loves playing
these power games at the company.
He just wants
the title of the Gao family's son-in-law
and my dad's money.
So let me ask you this.
Are you and Feng Shu really together?
What do you think?
Maybe he thinks so.
So let me ask you this.
Are you and Feng Shu really together?
Or at least,
in front of my dad.
That's because my dad
cut off all my cards before.
And our dance drama needed money urgently.
What could I do?
What was I supposed to say?
Plus, my dad was
lying in a hospital bed at the time.
Xingchen,
your little buddy here
is pretty smart.
See? Someone finally praised you.
Happy?
Happy.
I'll go get you some more hot water.
Okay.
Thanks.
No problem.
Let me ask you something.
See? Someone finally praised you.
Happy?
and he really
forced Yayan to get engaged to Feng Shu.
What would you do?
I had mentally prepared myself for that.
What could I do?
Just accept it.
Xingchen,
we've known each other for so many years
and been through so much.
Xingchen,
we've known each other for so many years
and been through so much.
Even if you lost Gao Yayan,
you could accept it calmly, right?
Then I lost my mother.
That incident back then
made me lose my father overnight.
And finally,
I lost you.
I accepted all of that calmly,
didn't I?
We are
all losing things,
Well said.
Thank you.
I'll pour.
So,
back to the topic, Captain Li.
You two grew up together
and have been friends for so many years.
Don't you know
what kind of person Yanfei is?
Don't listen to Feng Shu's nonsense.
Work call?
We'll give you some privacy.
I'll just take it outside.
Captain Li,
it's Li Fang.
What's up?
Did you remember something else?
Well,
I just
contacted my partner
who organized the competition
with me.
According to her memory,
Shen Xi really did meet Gao Yuhai.
But I really didn't know
about this before.
When
and where?
Can you elaborate?
How about this?
I'll ask her out
and we can talk in person.
Tell me
when and where.
We can go over anytime.
Okay.
Alright,
that's it for now.
Bye.
Thank you, Captain Li.
You're welcome.
Officers,
this is the partner
I told you about.
She's the choreographer,
Mu Liyan.
Hello, Ms. Mu.
Hello.
Ms. Mu,
you said Gao Yuhai and Shen Xi had met.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Did they interact much?
Did they talk?
They probably didn't interact much.
I remember at that time...
After the dance competition,
the performers were getting
ready to head back.
Suddenly, we were notified
to stay
for the celebration banquet.
Contestants,
let's give a warm round of applause
to welcome the Chairman of Wending Group,
the renowned entrepreneur,
Mr. Gao Yuhai.
Great!
Hello, Mr. Gao.
Mr. Mu.
Hello, I've heard so much about you.
Thank you for coming in person
despite your busy schedule.
Please, have a seat.
Alright, everyone, please sit.
To all the young, promising,
and energetic future dancers,
hello.
I'm so happy to see you all.
As soon as I sat down,
I felt
the color and radiance of youth,
as well as the vitality
and passion of the young.
I instantly felt
10 or 20 years younger.
Thank you, Mr. Gao,
for sponsoring our dance competition.
My pleasure.
Mr. Gao is forever young,
right?
Right.
Alright, let's give it up for Mr. Gao.
Thank you.
Song Yanfei   Wang Zhiyong (Wang Ruizi)
Gao Yayan   Zhang Ke
Xiao Ze   Wang Hao
Bai Xiaosi   Liu Xiaolong (Liu Xubai)
Mu Liyan   Chen Yongxia
Bai Jiuzhou   Qin Peng
Gao Yuhai   Cao Haitao (Cao Jingshi)
Cast (In order of strokes
of Chinese surnames)
Forensics Officer   Kang Hairu
Forensic Doctor   Cheng Gong
Young Bai Xiaosi   Zhang Weilun
Investor   Zha Minxin
Wu Dalong   Sui Dalong
Special/Extras
Police   Yang Menglin   Wang Yiguo
Xiao Ze's Father   He Meng
Xiao Ze's Relative
Hong Zhifeng
Dancer
Wang Shiwei
Lei
Li Xingchen's Mother   Tong
Little Buddy Xiao Ba   Niu Dali
Li Xingchen's Classmate
Tang Tang   Dai Guoming
Secretary   Qian Duo
Girl Ying Ying   Huang Mingfei
Fengshu's Secretary   Dai Dai
Getaway Driver   Liu Haohan
Speaking Police   Wang Zhiguo
Aunt Tu Manxia   Huang Xinyang
Mother   Liu Li
Middle-aged Man   Wang Xinda
Driver Lao Zhao   Wei Hong
Wei Hong
Locksmith   Fu Wang
Xiao Ze's Father   Zhou Wen
Xiao Ze's Mother   Pei Xiao
Speaking Girl
Young Man   Tang Yuye
Female Secretary   Qian Duoduo
Driver   Hu
Wounded   Xu Ganggang
Crane Operator   Wen
Yan's Mother   Zhang Minghui
Male Doctor   Wang Ke
Male Nurse   Wu Zeyu
Speaking Neighbor   Wu Meiling
BBQ Restaurant Guest   Cheng Gong
Speaking Contestant Nancy   Xu Ziyi
Bai Xiaosi's Stand-in   Zhao Peng
Cashier   Wu Tiantian
Female Police Officer   Wu Lihua
Forensic Doctor   Zhou Wen   Pei Xiao
Execution Doctor   Sister Geng
Cleaner   Liu Li
Streamer   Sun Jialiang
Extra Da Qing   Liu Haohan
Hotpot Restaurant Owner   Qin Haitao
Presenter   Sui Dalong   Yu Tianhang
Chief Distributor   Hu Kaichen
Hu Kaichen
Zhang Ningning
Daily Life Producer   Yin Zhongheng
On-set Producer   Hu Huazheng
Finance   Geng Yusa
Key Grip   Liu Yiqing
Grip   Xu Ganggang   Zhao Menglin
Kitchen Manager   Yin Xiumei
Wang Ji   Zhang Xiong
Li Xiaojun   Song Shuwei
Niu Yuwang   Wang Yiguo
Zhang Haiping   Cao Yongjie
Directing Team
Director   Yue Shunming
Co-Director   Xu
Executive Director   Sui Chenggong
Director's Assistant
Tang Yuye   Li Gaoyang
Casting Director Dai Guoming
Editing Team
Editor Wu Yingjie
Production Sound Equipment Provided by Beijing
Wenhui Qiming Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Sound Director Zhang Kai
Art and Props Team
Co-Production Designer Gong Xueyuan
Executive Art Director Wang Wenqi
Set Decorator Zhang Xueqi
Props Master Yang Xueshan
Action Props Wu Tai
On-Set Supervisor Hou Yonghao
Set Dressers Zhang Li, Zhang Qingzhong
Camera A Operator He Yong
Camera A Focus Puller Yao Yonglei
Camera B Operator Zhao Shidian
Camera B Focus Puller Li Chenlong
Camera C Operator Ma Mingguo
Camera C Focus Puller Xie Xiaozhong
Camera Assistant
Still Photographer Dong Guiping
Gaffer Gao Yun
Best Boys Zhang Xiaoguang, Chang Lin
Terigun
Styling Team
Styling Director Gao Bin
On-Set Hair & Makeup Supervisor Li Zixu
On-Set Wardrobe Zhang Tingting,
Qiu Yaqiong
Beijing This Is Cola Culture
Media Co., Ltd.
Planning Director Yang Liuting
Copywriters Zhang Weirui, Li Ziwei
Video Editors Wang Jiahui, Miao Wenbo
Beijing Wenhui Qiming Culture
Communication Co., Ltd.
Post-Production Supervisor Wu Wenhui
Colorist Niu Xuerui
Assistant Colorist Dong Jiayi
End Credits Jin Linxin
Trailer Production Li
Dialog Editor Dong Xuebing
Sound Effects Editor Zhang Xiaoman
Compositors Gao Dong, Wu Yingjie
Shang Chenyao
Music Director Xiao Zhuang
Music Coordinators Jiang Zheng, Liu Zining
Music Editor
Female Humming Ma Qianran
Songs
Vocals Yue
Lyrics Yue Shunming
Arranger Zhao Yi
Producer Xiao Zhuang
Children's Vocals Zhang Maolin
Arranger Xiao Zhuang
Vocals
Lyrics Bai Yuxiang
Arranger
Producer Xiao Zhuang
Lyrics Xu Yue
Vocals Xu Yue
Lyrics Gao Jingman
Arranger Wang Anyu
Producer Xu Yue
Composer Xu Yue
"The More I Love, The More I'm Wrong"
Vocals Wang Weijia
Composer Xiao Zhuang
Arranger Zhao Yi
Vocals Liu Ruixun
Lyrics Bai Yuxiang
Arranger Zhao Yi
Producer Xiao Zhuang
Special Thanks
Shiyan Public Security Bureau
Fangxian Lulingwang Liquor Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Sinopharm Dongfeng Huaguo Hospital
Dongfang Yuanzhi School,
Maojian District, Shiyan
Hubei Zesheng Property Service Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Mingxin Huizhi Dance Academy
Shiyan Haishuo Loading and Unloading
Machinery Co., Ltd.
Exclusive Social Media Platform
Weibo
Chief Media Partners
Sina Entertainment, Weibo TV, Sina TV
Beijing Sui Brothers Film
and Television Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Co-Producers
Shanxi Chengyi Film
and Television Media Co., Ltd.,
Songyuan Senshengda Economic
and Trade Co., Ltd.